JEROME FERNANDEZ

UX/UI DESIGNER & WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am a passionate and driven Graphic Designer and Print/Electronic Production specialist with over 10 years of experience creating visually stunning and engaging designs. Currently, I am a student at Fanshawe College in London, Ontario, pursuing my passion for Interactive Media Design. I am expected to complete my program and graduate in April 2023.

I am excited to pursue a career path as a Full Stack Developer. With my background in Graphic Design and extensive experience in Electronic Production, I am confident in my ability to bring a unique perspective and skill set to this field. I have gained valuable experience working in Advertising Agency environments, collaborating with cross-functional teams to create exceptional designs that meet client needs and exceed expectations. I am always eager to learn and grow as a designer and developer and am excited for the opportunities that lie ahead.

SKILLS

Web Design
Web Development
UX/UI
Video Editing
Logo Design
Motion Graphics
Retoucher
Graphic Design & Layout

CONTACTS



519-532-5410



fernandezjerome 0824@gmail.com



london, Ontario

SOCIAL MEDIA



www.linkedin.com/in/jerome-fernandez-81253b14



www.jerome-fernandez.ca

EXPERIENCES

OCT 2014 - OCT 2021

STAR INC.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER/VIDEO EDITOR

As a Graphic Designer and Video Editor at Star Inc., I design layouts for digital and print media and create engaging promotional videos. I collaborate with the marketing team to ensure designs align with the brand and meet the needs of the company and its customers. My role requires technical and creative skills, as well as collaboration with cross-functional teams to deliver high-quality designs and videos.

JAN 2014 - SEPT 2014

DENTSU PHILIPPINES

DIGITAL IMAGING ARTIST/RETOUCHER

I was responsible for retouching and enhancing digital images used in the company's brochures, billboards, and print ads. My role required technical expertise in photo editing software such as Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign as well as a keen eye for detail to ensure the images met the company's high standards. I collaborated with the design team to deliver visually compelling marketing materials that effectively promoted the company's products and services.

APR 2012 - DEC 2013

SUSHI GRAPHICS

DIGITAL IMAGING ARTIST/RETOUCHER

As an Digital Imaging Specialist at Sushi Graphics, I worked in-house for Publicis JimenezBasic, creating brochures, billboards, and print ads that required digital imaging and retouching. My role required expertise in photo editing software such as Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign, as well as a keen eye for detail to ensure the images met the company's high standards. I collaborated with the design team to deliver visually compelling marketing materials that effectively promoted the company's products and services.

EDUCATION

2022 - 2023

FANSHAWE COLLEGE

INTERACTIVE MEDIA DESIGN

London, Ontario

AMA UNIVERSITY

COMPUTER SCIENCE

Cebu City, Philippines

SOFTWARES

Adobe InDesign Adobe Premier Pro

Adobe PhotoShop Adobe XD

Adobe Illustrator MS Office suite

Adobe After Effects Cinema 4D

WEB TOOLS

Visual Studio Code Node.js
HTML/CSS Lumen
JavaScript Php
Greensock Github
Vue.js Wordpress